My brother, you listened to the message today?
Yes, sir.
What are you taking home?
I'm taking home the fact that I must deny myself, carry my cross and follow Jesus.
But before now, you were born again?
Yes, Man of God. Ok!
Ok. But now, you have not denied yourself, have you?
Yes.
You want to go and deny yourself now?
Yes, Man of God.
How do you deny yourself?
By giving total commitment to God, and not just lip service.
There is an injection you were taking before, that used to make you high.
I am happy you have realised that you need to deny yourself and take up your cross.
Yes, Man of God.
Not just accept Jesus as your Lord and Saviour.
If you say you accept Jesus genuinely, commitment would ask Jesus to accept you, to take you.
The commitment is the one that will introduce you, not the acceptance.
When you say, "I accept Jesus as my Lord and Saviour" truly, genuinely,
but the commitment would now be the one to introduce you, "Jesus, ok, this is a beloved one".
Your healing - because you want to live for God.
Amen.
Ok? That is why they cannot ask you, "Where is the money?
Bring money, food, bring this, bring that!" - no!
Because to live for God - that is why you are receiving this healing.
Come on!
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Healing And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Healed of Difficulty In Walking Due to Fracture of the Femur - No Longer Using a Crutch
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus, I can walk now.
TESTIMONY TIME
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Emmanuel, People of God!
My name is Derek Miranda, I'm a Zimbabwean that's currently residing in Kenya.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN is that of difficulty in walking caused by a broken femur.
I sustained a broken femur earlier this year from an accident that occurred whilst I was running.
As a result of that accident, I was impaired; I spent a month out of work.
And the pain that followed was unbearable.
It stopped me from enjoying the simple things in life.
I could not move with freedom. I could not sit or stand for too long.
My entire existence reminded me of the fact that I had a broken leg and I was in pain.
So, it affected my work and I was highly dependent on drugs to help me cope with the pain.
That is what brought me to The SCOAN in pursuit of a solution.
So as a result of my injury, I had to use crutches to help me with my mobility if I wanted to go places.
I couldn't lift my leg, I had to drag it along; it had lost muscle strength and power.
So, I had seen multiple orthopedic surgeons in different countries such as Kenya and South Africa.
But the last orthopedic surgeon that we consulted indicated that I needed to go back into surgery.
Once I returned to my original orthopedic surgeon, he advised me that he saw nothing wrong.
So, it was a conflict in medical opinion over my situation.
Therefore, I decided that I was going to consult and seek the Word of God over my life and situation.
And that is what brought me here to The SCOAN.
When I came here, by the grace of God, the man of God located me.
When he located me, he came towards me and he started ministering towards me.
He told me that it is not the acceptance of Jesus Christ that brings Him to the scene.
It is your total commitment to Him that brings Him to the scene.
And once he did that, he also prophesied upon my life and
he indicated the fact that I had been using drugs that made me high.
I confirm this prophecy to be true at this point because I've been highly dependent on codeine
as a substance to help me cope with pain.
As soon as the man of God was done ministering to me - I don´t even think he touched me,
he just stretched his hand towards me and instantly, I felt an unspeakable surge of power
go through my entire body, go through my entire being
and I do not remember what happened.
All I know is that I felt that power.
When I stood up, it was as if something had left me and I was finding myself again.
That's what happened.
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
Healed of Difficulty in Walking Due to Fracture - No longer Using a Crutch
So, you mean, you felt that overwhelming power - the presence of God?
And when you stood up, what happened?
When I stood up, I stood up with a renewed sense of energy.
My bones felt really strengthened to a point where I could stand on one leg which I could never do before.
Just for dressing up, I had to sit on the bed.
But now, I can actually stand on the leg that was previously injured.
So I felt a large sense of renewal within my entire being.
So, you mean now that all the things you could not do before, you can now do them?
And the pain is now a thing of the past?
Yes, pain is now a thing of the past, in Jesus' mighty name!
Amen! Put your hands together for Jesus!
Healed of Difficulty in Walking Due to Fracture in Femur - No longer Using a Crutch
Yes. To the glory of God, can you now move and let us see what the Lord has done in your life?
Healed of Difficulty in Walking Due to Fracture in Femur - No Longer Using a Crutch
Can you still feel the pain as you're moving?
There is no pain whatsoever.
To God be the glory.
Healed of Difficulty in Walking Due to Fracture in Femur - No Longer Using a Crutch
And remember, in your testimony, you said you were addicted to codeine because of this terrible pain.
So now, are you still addicted to drugs now? Are you still having that issue?
No, I have no desire to take drugs.
The enemy tried to tempt me with a headache but I couldn't even take painkillers to treat that headache.
So, I have no affinity or desire towards taking any drugs. I am pain-free and drug-free.
Wow.
Healed of Difficulty in Walking Due to Fracture in Femur - No Longer Using a Crutch
The advice that I have for them is the same advice that the Prophet gave last week:
That it is not just acceptance of Christ Jesus; it is your total commitment to Jesus Christ.
Denying yourself is what compels Jesus to approach and come on the scene.
So, be committed to God, like the man of God said. It is not only accepting Him
as your Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, but be totally committed to Him with your body, spirit and soul
and it shall be well with you in Jesus' name.
TT: Jacqueline Margaret Fernandez
RV: Esther Mwelwa + Mel Flowers 3/9/2018